Contact

doctorDAlvarez@protonmail.c

www.linkedin.com/in/ doctordalvarez (LinkedIn) neuroreact.dev (Personal) doctordalvarez.hashnode.dev/ (Blog) twitter.com/doctordalvarez (Personal)

Top Skills

Front-end Development
React.js
Python (Programming Language)

Certifications

Full Stack JavaScript Techdegree SQL FUNDAMENTALS Python Web Developer LPI Linux Essentials (010-160) PYTHON FOR DATA SCIENCE: FUNDAMENTALS

Diego Alvarez

React developer

Buenos Aires

Summary

I'm a React developer

Evolved problem solving skills with the years learning algorithms with different programming languages and paradigms. Always digest problems into fragments, in a deterministic and declarative approach.

I love to learn by teaching and coding.

Experience with C/C++, python, HTML5, CSS3 and javaScript: ES6.

Experience with React and Redux: State management, Context API, optimization with memoized techniques, colocation and composability, styled-components(emotion), Gatsby, Next, Jest, Mocka.

Experience with Hooks.

Building my custom hooks library.

I am looking to:

- Write and learn as much I can about React and JS.
- Get senior experience in the field.
- Collaborating with startups and open-source.
- Improve the healthcare industry, developing innovative tools and resources.
- Make the world a healthy place.

www.neuroreact.dev (0.1.0)(Building)

Thanks for visiting.

Diego.

Experience

Visiva Design Frontend Web Developer January 2019 - January 2021 (2 years 1 month)

Buenos Aires Province, Argentina

Improve UX/UI for clients using React and Redux.

SEO

Experience with debugging and performance testing software.

www.visivaestudio.com.ar

HTML5 - CSS3 - ES6 - REACT - REDUX - JEST

Honda Motor de Argentina Healthcare Management Specialist January 2010 - April 2011 (1 year 4 months) Campana, Buenos Aires Province, Argentina

ACLS: Advance Cardiovascular Life Support.

Trained employees (engineers, plant workers, administrative and human resources department) in ACLS protocols and simulation scenarios. Improved the factory overall understanding and handling of unexpected cardiac events.

Education

Harvard Extension School

Computer Science and Web Development · (January 2019 - December 2020)

Treehouse

Full Stack Javascript Techdegree (January 2021 - June 2021)

React Hooks Workshop w/ Ryan Florence

Workshop, React Programming · (June 2021 - July 2021)

Zero To Mastery Academy

Python developer, Computer Programming, Specific

Applications · (2020 - 2020)

University of Buenos Aires

Doctor of Medicine - Ph.D., Anesthesiology - Pain medicine · (2011 - 2016)